Guide to the Trinity College of Arts and Sciences, Office of the Dean records, 1911-2006 UA.25.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List
  - Thinking about Ourselves: Black Women and Feminist Thought, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Reproductive Rights and the Pro-Choice Perspective, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Multiple Personality and Demonological Possession, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Methodist Theology and History, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Men and Gender Issues, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Exploring Violence Against Women: A Feminist Introduction, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Women and the Law, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Women of Color: Feminist Perspectives, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Health Care and Power Relations in Eastern North Carolina, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Partnership for Literacy, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Human Sexuality: A Study of the Presbyterian Church, USA's Controversial Paper, Keeping Body and Soul Together: Sexuality, Spirituality, and Social Justice, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Getting High in America, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Honduras: Toward Christian Understanding, 1992 (Box 145)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Human Rights Agenda for the 1990s, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Exploring the Links between Environmental Issues and Social Justice, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Cooperative Living for a Better Environment, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Education Students At-Risk, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Homelessness in NYC, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Social Issues and Health Care in Eastern North Carolina, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Balancing Career and Personal Relationships: Exploring Options for Life after Duke, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Women and the Law, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Men and Gender Issues, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Project Wild, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Perspectives on Iranian Culture, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Indigent Health Care and Power Relations in the US, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Whose Health is It Anyway: Women and Health Care from a Feminist Perspective, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Visibility and Voice through Performance Event Art: "We are Secretaries", 1992 (Box 145)
  - Literacy through Photography: Teaching Photography and Writing in Elementary and Middle Schools, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Thinking about Ourselves: Surviving as Black Women in Today's Society, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Latin American Policy: The Environmental Policy of the Amazon, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Presbyterian Perspectives: Past and Present, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Migrant Farmworkers in NC, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Youth in Crisis: Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 145)
  - A Christian Critique of Modernity: The Ethics of Stanley Hauerwas, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Human Sexuality and Abortion: A Study of Two Documents of the Presbyterian Church (USA), 1992 (Box 145)
  - Young and Black: The Coming of Age of Black Youth, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Men and Gender Issues, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Women and the Law, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Thinking about Ourselves: Surviving as Black Women, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Health Care and Power Relations in Eastern N.C., 1992 (Box 145)
  - Honduras: Toward Understanding, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Health Care and Power Relations in North Carolina, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Writing: Beginning the Creative Process, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Healing the Homeless: Indigent Health Care and Power Relations in the US, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Finding a Theory of Community Education, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Into the Fields: Migrant Workers in NC, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Project Wild, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Women, Eating and Society, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Women and the Law, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Thinking about Ourselves: Surviving as Black Women in Today's Society, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Women in Leadership: Contemporary Issues in US Policy and Culture, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Men and Gender Issues, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Balancing Career and Personal Relationships: Exploring Options for Life after Duke, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Mentors and Moms: Adolescent Pregnancy, Social Policy and Social Responsibility, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Cooperative Living for a Better Environment, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Partnership for Literacy: Education and Employment Issues, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Liberal Arts Epistemology, 1993 (Box 145)
  - Modern Greek: Language and Culture, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Health Care and Power Relations in Eastern NC, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Women and the Law, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Men and Gender Issues, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Sexual Issues and Their Impact on the Duke Community, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Using Theater for Social Awareness and Change, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Developing Self, Mind and Voice: Women and Knowing, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Race and Education in America, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Multiculturalism in Organizations: Theory and Practice, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Race Relations at Duke, 1993 (Box 146)
  - House Course Not Approved, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Issues in German Current Affairs, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Honduras: Toward a Christian Understanding of It, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Bolivia: A Christian Understanding of Its Health Care, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Palestine and Israel: A Journey of Understanding and Reconciliation, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Into the Fields: Farmworkers in NC, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Project Wild, 1994 (Box 146)
  - An Educational Perspective on Bob Dylan and the History of Western Philosophy, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Education Kids, Ourselves and Our Communities, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Partnership for Literacy: Education and Employment Issues, 1994 (Box 146)
  - The American Courtroom: Theory and Practice, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Contemporary Issues in the US Latino Community, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Health Care and Power Relations in Rural NC, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Race Relations at Duke, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Writing: Beginning the Creative Process, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Liberal Arts Epistemology: A Senior's Guide to Intellectualism, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Business Organizations and Competition: Critical Cases, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Sexual Issues and Their Impact on the Duke Community, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Expressing Ourselves: Black Women Novelists, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Women, Eating and Society, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Ecofeminism, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Women and the Law, 1994 (Box 146)
  - The Other Durham: Problems of Urban Life, 1994 (Box 146)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Women, Eating and Society, 1994 (Box 146)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Environmental Issues and Social Justice, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Health Care and Power Relations in Eastern North Carolina, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Race Relations at Duke, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Women and the Law, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Generation X: Growing Up in the 90s and Beyond, 1994 (Box 146)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Faces of Chiapas, Mexico, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Globalization and Alternative Visions for the Future, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Educating Kids, Ourselves and Our Communities, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Honduras: An Introduction to the Realities of the Poor, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Women and the Law, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Housing and Homelessness, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Creating More Space: The Expression of a Black Women's Community, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Into the Fields: Farmworkers in North and South Carolina, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Guyana: Missions in Historical, Cultural and Political Context, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Topics in Gay, Lesbian and Bisexual Legal Issues, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Durham Community Building, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Project Wild, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Confronting the Issues in US Latino Communities, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Partnership for Literacy: Education and Employment Issues, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Health Policy and Power Relations in Eastern NC, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Generation X: Problems and Solutions of our Times, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Women and the Law, 1995 (Box 146)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Examining Malcolm X: The Life and Portrayal of a Black Leader, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Health Care and Power Relations in Eastern NC, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Our Disembodied Body: Issues in Disordered Eating, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Confronting the Issues of Elementary Education, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Tom Clancy and the New World Order, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Environmental Issues and Social Justice, 1995 (Box 146)
  - House Course not Approved, 1995 (Box 146)
  - The Theology of C. S. Lewis in The Chronicles of Narnia, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Rethinking Documentary: Latino Communities in North Carolina, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Gay, Lesbian and Bisexual Legal Issues, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Honduras: Towards a Christian Understanding, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Refugee Policy: The Balkan Conflict, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Gangster Films, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Into the Fields: Farmworkers in North and South Carolina, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Our Disembodied Body, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Judaism and Gender: Explorations, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Reflections of Colorful Faces: An in Depth Look at Minorities in Advertising, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Guyana: Missions in Historical, Cultural and Political Context, 1996 (Box 147)
  - African-American Psychology, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Student Leadership and Community Action, 1996 (Box 147)
  - The Language of Music, 1996 (Box 147)
  - The Myths and Realities of Hypnosis, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Student Activism: National Issues, Politics and Action at Duke, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Native American Issues and the State of the Reservation, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Women and the Law, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Community Empowerment/Health Care Issues, 1996 (Box 147)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Black and Whites: Separate and Hostile?, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Partnership for Literacy: Education and Employment, 1996 (Box 147)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Project Wild: An Introduction to Experimental Education, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Housing and Homelessness, 1996 (Box 147)
  - AIDS: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow, 1996 (Box 147)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1996 (Box 147)
  - The Environment in Latin America: A Quest Toward Sustainability, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Connecting Souls? The African-American Experience in Russia, 1996 (Box 147)
  - The Theology of C. S. Lewis in The Chronicles of Narnia, 1996 (Box 147)
  - An Introduction to ASL and Deaf Culture, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Issues of Identity and Gender in Recent Asian American Literature, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Our Disembodied Bodies: Issues in Disordered Eating, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Animal Rights, Ethics and Public Policy, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Women and the Law, 1996 (Box 147)
  - HIV Positive Children in America, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Health Care and Power Relations in Eastern NC, 1996 (Box 147)
  - Honduras: Towards a Christian Understanding, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Project Wild: An Introduction to Experiential Education, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Sexual Violence: A Social Problem with Social Solutions, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Verses and Reverses: Feminist Perspectives in Communities of Faith, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Our Disembodied Body, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Dreams, 1997 (Box 147)
  - AIDS: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Speaking for America's Children: Education, Health Care and Community Advocacy, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Bosnian Refugee and Development Policy, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Race and Religion in America, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Native American Issues, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Ain't I a Woman? Multiple Perspectives on Feminism, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Aliens Attack! The Metaphor of Alien Invasion in Film, 1997 (Box 147)
  - An Introduction to American Sign Language and Deaf Culture Section 1, 1997 (Box 147)
  - An Introduction to American Sign Language and Deaf Culture Section 2, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Environmental Issues and Social Justice, 1997 (Box 147)
  - The Theology of C. S. Lewis in The Chronicles of Narnia, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Housing and Homelessness, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Into the Fields: Farmworkers in North and South Carolina, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Men and Masculinities, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Animal Rights, Ethics and Public Policy, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Devilnet: Publishing Duke's Virtual Community, 1997 (Box 147)
  - What is Zen?, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Star Wars as a Religious Saga, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Health Care and Power Relations in Eastern North Carolina, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Alternative Medicine and the Art of Healing, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Interpretation of Dreams, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Women and the Law, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Our Disembodied Bodies: Issues in Disordered Eating, 1997 (Box 147)
  - The Theology of C. S. Lewis in The Chronicles of Narnia, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Sexual Violence: A Social Problem with Social Solutions, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Men and Masculinities, 1997 (Box 147)
  - An Introduction to American Sign Language and Deaf Culture, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Domestic and Relationship Violence: 'Till Death Do Us Part?, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Women and Politics: One Woman, One Vote, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Health Care and Power Relations in Eastern North Carolina, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Glimpses of the Self, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Sexuality, Gender and Popular Culture, 1997 (Box 147)
  - Black Woman: Psychology of Self Definition, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Violence Against Women, An International Perspective, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Honduras: Towards a Christian Understanding, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Maya Art and Archaeology, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Physics for Pyros: Wacky Demonstrations and Experiments in Everyday Science, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Women and Politics: One Women, One Vote, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Grateful Dead: Culture, Music and Sociological Impact, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Noam Chomsky: Life of Dissent, 1998 (Box 148)
  - The Art of Healing: Integrating Spirit, Mind and Body in Medicine, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Leadership, Service and Social Change, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Our Disembodied Body: Issues in Disordered Eating, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Sexual Violence: A Social Problem with Social Solutions, 1998 (Box 148)
  - The Changing Face of AIDS in the US: Policy and Care in the 90s, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Housing and Homelessnes, 1998 (Box 148)
  - The Theology of C. S. Lewis in The Chronicles of Narnia, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Domestic Violence, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Relating Learning and Service, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Race and Religion in America: We Got the Power!, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Bob Marley and the Future of Decolonization, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Till Death Do us Part? A Course on Domestic and Relationship Violence, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Native American Issues, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Into the Fields: Farmworkers in North Carolina and South Carolina, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Women and the Law, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Project Wild: An Introduction to Experiential Education, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Octavia Butler: Representations of Minority Women in Science Fiction, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Cultures through Film, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Psychology of RAP, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Great Directors, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Health Care and Power Relations in Eastern NC, 1998 (Box 148)
  - AIDS: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow, 1998 (Box 148)
  - The United Nations: Past, Present and Future?, 1998 (Box 148)
  - The Art of Healing: Integrating Spirit, Mind and Body in Medicine, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Relating Learning and Service, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Peer Education: Theories and Practice, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Azucar! Salsa: It's Origins, Evolution and Future, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Our Disembodied Body: Issues in Disordered Eating, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Baldwin Scholarship, 1978-1992 (Box 149)
  - Beinecke Scholarship, 1988-1994 (Box 149)
  - Brinkley Scholarship, 1988-1993 (Box 149)
  - Janet B. Chiang Memorial Scholarship, 1988-1993 (Box 149)
  - CIC Memorial Fellowship, 1984-1985 (Box 149)
  - Cranmer Scholarship, 1970-1993 (Box 149)
  - Faculty Scholarships, 1988-1989 (Box 149)
  - Javits Fellowship, 1994-1995 (Box 149)
  - Liggett Scholarships, 1977-1990 (Box 149)
  - MacFarlane Scholarships, 1984-1993 (Box 149)
  - James Madison Fellowship, 1992 (Box 149)
  - Mellon Fellowship, 1986-1994 (Box 149)
  - Academic Achievement Award, 1984-1985 (Box 150)
  - North Carolina Chapter of AISP Scholarship, 1984 (Box 150)
  - Panhellenic Scholarship, 1987-1992 (Box 150)
  - Pillsbury Scholarship, 1985 (Box 150)
  - Truman Scholarship, 1987-1995 (Box 150)
  - USA Today Award, 1992-1995 (Box 150)
  - AAS, 1978-1994 (Box 151)
  - African and Afro-American Studies, 1976-1984 (Box 151)
  - Air Science, 1983-1993 (Box 151)
  - Aerospace Studies, 1975-1985 (Box 151)
  - American Dance Festival, 1978-1993 (Box 151)
  - Anthropology, 1974-1994 (Box 151)
  - Asian and African Languages and Literature, 1990-1994 (Box 151)
  - Arabic, 1981-1989 (Box 151)
  - Chinese, 1980-1994 (Box 151)
  - Hebrew, 1985-1994 (Box 151)
  - Hindi, 1983-1995 (Box 151)
  - Japanese, 1983-1994 (Box 151)
  - Korean, 1990-1992 (Box 151)
  - Persian, 1978-1987 (Box 151)
  - Swahili, 1985-1992 (Box 151)
  - Art, 1979-1994 (Box 151)
  - Art History, 1978-1994 (Box 151)
  - Institute of the Arts, 1981-1994 (Box 151)
  - Biological Anthropology and Anatomy, 1991-1992 (Box 151)
  - Biology, 1982-1994 (Box 151)
  - Botany, 1975-1989 (Box 151)
  - Canadian Studies, 1990-1994 (Box 151)
  - Chemistry, 1973-1994 (Box 151)
  - Classical Studies, 1976-1994 (Box 151)
  - Computer Science, 1974-1994 (Box 151)
  - Comparative Area Studies, 1991-1994 (Box 151)
  - Cultural Anthropology, 1990-1995 (Box 151)
  - Dance, 1981-1994 (Box 151)
  - Drama, 1978-1995 (Box 152)
  - DPC, 1975-1994 (Box 152)
  - Economics, 1969-1995 (Box 152)
  - Education, 1975-1994 (Box 152)
  - English, 1981-1995 (Box 152)
  - Environment, School of, 1990-1994 (Box 152)
  - FOCUS Programs, 1991-1994 (Box 152)
  - Geology, 1978-1995 (Box 152)
  - Genetics, 1980-1988 (Box 152)
  - German, 1977-1994 (Box 152)
  - Yiddish, 1973-1991 (Box 152)
  - Health, PE and Recreation: Changes since August 1981, 1981-1994 (Box 152)
  - Health, PE and Recreation: Correspondence, 1973-1981 (Box 152)
  - P.E. Correspondence, 1979-1997 (Box 152)
  - History, 1972-1994 (Box 152)
  - History, 1964-1994 (Box 153)
  - Interdisciplinary Course, IDC, 1980-1993 (Box 153)
  - Judaic Studies, 1988-1989 (Box 153)
  - Linguistics, 1990 (Box 153)
  - Literature, 1976-1995 (Box 153)
  - Management Science, 1980-1993 (Box 153)
  - Marine Sciences, 1977-1983 (Box 153)
  - Math, 1973-1994 (Box 153)
  - Anatomy, 1979-1988 (Box 153)
  - Biochemistry, 1978-1994 (Box 153)
  - Cell and Molecular Biology, 1989-1993 (Box 153)
  - Microbiology and Immunology, 1983-1992 (Box 153)
  - Neurobiology, 1991-1994 (Box 153)
  - Pathology, 1984-1988 (Box 153)
  - Pharmacology, 1988-1994 (Box 153)
  - Physiology, 1973-1987 (Box 153)
  - Medieval and Renaissance Studies, 1989-1994 (Box 153)
  - Military Science, 1983-1987 (Box 153)
  - Music, 1973-1994 (Box 153)
  - Naval Science, 1981-1990 (Box 153)
  - Philosophy, 1976-1993 (Box 153)
  - Physics, 1973-1994 (Box 153)
  - Political Science, 1975-1995 (Box 153)
  - Psychology, 1974-1994 (Box 153)
  - Public Policy, 1975-1995 (Box 153)
  - Religion, 1972-1994 (Box 154)
  - Romance Studies: Italian, 1968-1993 (Box 154)
  - Romance Studies: French, 1973-1994 (Box 154)
  - Romance Languages: Portuguese, 1974-1994 (Box 154)
  - Romance Languages: Spanish, 1973-1994 (Box 154)
  - Polish/Slavic, 1983-1992 (Box 154)
  - Russian, 1988-1994 (Box 154)
  - Serbian and Croatian, 1992-1995 (Box 154)
  - Ukrainian, 1992 (Box 154)
  - Sociology, 1981-1995 (Box 154)
  - UWC, 1985-1994 (Box 154)
  - Institute for Stats and Decision Sciences, 1985-1992 (Box 154)
  - Women's Studies, 1991-1994 (Box 154)
  - Evaluations [House Courses], 1999 (Box 154)
  - Memos Sent Out Regarding Evaluations, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Faculty Instructions, 1999 (Box 154)
  - House Courses: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 154)
  - House Courses: Information and Application Original, 1994-1997 (Box 154)
  - The Art of Healing: Integrating Spirit, Mind and Body in Medicine, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Azucar! Salsa: Its Origins, Evolution and Future, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Childhood Trauma and Recovery, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Economics: The Epic Tale, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Experience as Education: Project Wild, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Grateful Dead: Counter Culture, Music and Sociological Impact, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Great Faith, Great Doubt: The Search for Truth in Modern Times, 1999 (Box 154)
  - HealthCare and Power Relations in Eastern North Carolina, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Honduras: Towards a Christian Understanding, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Legal Rights and Gender Issues: Does Sex Matter?, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Our Disembodied Bodies: Issues in Disordered Eating, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Physics for Pyros, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Project B.U.I.L.D. House Course: Duke-Durham Relations, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Relative Learning and Service, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Service Opportunities in Leadership, SOL, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Sexual Violence: A Social Problem with Social Solutions, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Sweatshops, Duke and the Global Economy, 1999 (Box 154)
  - The Social Construction of AIDS, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Child Advocacy: Issues Facing America's Children BREAK FOR A CHANGE, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Domestic Violence BREAK FOR A CHANGE, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Homelessness and Poverty BREAK FOR A CHANGE, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Native American Issues BREAK FOR A CHANGE, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Race, Ethnicity and Social Reform BREAK FOR A CHANGE, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Welfare Reform BREAK FOR A CHANGE, 1999 (Box 154)
  - American Sign Language II, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Appalachian History and Culture: Intro to, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Our Disembodied Bodies: Issues in Disordered Eating, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Ethics and Peer Education, 1999 (Box 154)
  - HealthCare and Power Relations in Eastern North Carolina, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Holistic Living: Integrating Spirit, Mind and Body in Healing, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Juggling A Sudden Gust of Gravity: The Physics, History and Technique of Juggling," 1999 (Box 154)
  - Programming Windows with MFC: Intro to, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Sexual Violence: A Social Problem with Social Solutions, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Masculinity and Gender Roles, 1999 (Box 154)
  - Course Committee, 1978-1987 (Box 155)
  - Xerox of Part of 84-85 Course Committee Report, 1984-1985 (Box 155)
  - JY's File [John Younger] Course Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 155)
  - Inactive Courses, 1981 (Box 155)
  - COC, 1972-1973 (Box 155)
  - House Course Form and Info (Box 155)
  - COC file, 1972 (Box 155)
  - PE Courses, 1984 (Box 155)
  - Disposition of Historical Course Committee Files, 1984 (Box 155)
  - Computer Abbreviations, 1980 (Box 155)
  - Committee on Courses of Instruction: General Correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box 155)
  - Arabic, 1980-1984 (Box 156)
  - Biology, 1974-1983 (Box 156)
  - Botany, 1977-1984 (Box 156)
  - Chinese, 1976-1985 (Box 156)
  - Hindi-Urdu, 1963-1981 (Box 156)
  - Korean, 1986 (Box 156)
  - Asian and African Languages: Persian and Swahili, 1979 (Box 156)
  - Chemistry, 1977-1982 (Box 156)
  - Classical Studies, 1968-1985 (Box 156)
  - Greek, 1968-1986 (Box 156)
  - Latin, 1981-1986 (Box 156)
  - Computer Science, 1980-1985 (Box 156)
  - Dance Program, 1981-1984 (Box 156)
  - Distinguished Professor, 1981-1985 (Box 156)
  - Drama, 1975-1986 (Box 156)
  - Economics, 1971-1986 (Box 156)
  - Forestry, 1971-1985 (Box 156)
  - English, 1973-1986 (Box 156)
  - Geology, 1969-1984 (Box 156)
  - German, 1973-1982 (Box 156)
  - History, 1976-1985 (Box 156)
  - HPRE, 1979-1981 (Box 156)
  - IDC, 1981-1986 (Box 156)
  - Japanese, 1971-1981 (Box 156)
  - Korean, 1986 (Box 156)
  - Linguistics, 1961-1970 (Box 156)
  - Literature, 1961-1985 (Box 156)
  - Math, 1982-1984 (Box 156)
  - Management Services, 1979-1981 (Box 156)
  - Marine Sciences, 1979-1981 (Box 156)
  - Mathematics, 1977-1985 (Box 157)
  - Anatomy, 1979-1985 (Box 157)
  - Biochemistry, 1979-1980 (Box 157)
  - Microbiology and Immunology, 1978-1981 (Box 157)
  - Physiology, 1981-1986 (Box 157)
  - Military Science, 1984 (Box 157)
  - Music, 1972-1986 (Box 157)
  - Naval Science, 1976-1985 (Box 157)
  - Philosophy, 1971-1979 (Box 157)
  - Physics, 1967-1986 (Box 157)
  - Political Science, 1975-1986 (Box 157)
  - Psychology, 1969-1986 (Box 157)
  - Public Policy, 1970-1985 (Box 157)
  - Religion, 1972-1984 (Box 157)
  - Romance Languages, 1972-1984 (Box 157)